import {
  iconAngry,
  iconEmotional,
  iconHappy,
  iconNeutral,
  iconSad,
  avatarImage1,
  avatarImage2,
  avatarImage3,
  avatarImage4,
  avatarImage5,
  avatarImage6,
} from "../assets";

export const selfCareFeeling = [
  ["Happy", iconHappy],
  ["Neutral", iconNeutral],
  ["Emotional", iconEmotional],
  ["Sad", iconSad],
  ["Angry", iconAngry],
  ["Overwhelming", iconAngry],
];

export const dashboardQuotes = [
  [
    "Mental health...is not a destination, but a process. It's about how you drive, not where you're going.",
    "Noam Shpancer",
  ],
  [
    "You are enough just as you are. Each emotion you feel, everything in your life, everything you do or do not do...where you are and who you are right now is enough. It is perfect.",
    "Haemin Sunim",
  ],

  [
    "The strongest people are not those who show strength in front of us but those who win battles we know nothing about.",
    "Jonathan Harnisch",
  ],
  [
    "Your illness does not define you. Your strength and courage does.",
    "Unknown",
  ],
  [
    "You don't have to be positive all the time. It's perfectly okay to feel sad, angry, annoyed, frustrated, scared, or anxious. Having feelings doesn't make you a negative person. It makes you human.",
    "Lori Deschene",
  ],
  [
    "Self-care is not selfish. You cannot serve from an empty vessel.",
    "Eleanor Brownn",
  ],
  ["You are the sky. Everything else – it's just the weather.", "Pema Chödrön"],
  [
    "It is okay to be at a place of struggle. It is okay to be a work in progress. It is okay to be on a journey.",
    "Unknown",
  ],
  [
    "You, as much as anybody in the entire universe, deserve your love and affection.",
    "Buddha",
  ],
];

export const selfCareConcern = [
  ["Anxiety", " bg-[#DFE7FD] ", "/therapy/anxiety"],
  ["Stress", " bg-[#FCF6BD] ", "/therapy/stress"],
  ["Depression", " bg-[#B9FBC0] ", "/therapy/depression"],
  ["Panic Attacks", " bg-[#9BF6FF] ", "/therapy/panic-attack"],
  ["Conduct Disorder", " bg-[#FFCFD2] ", "/therapy/conduct-disorder"],
  ["Bipolar Disorder", " bg-[#98F5E1] ", "/therapy/bipolar-disorder"],
  ["Eating Disorder", " bg-[#FFDE8C] ", "/therapy/eating-disorder"],
  ["Anger Issues", " bg-[#C9C0FA] ", "/therapy/anger"],
];

export const RoutineCareChats = [
  {
    question: "What is Self - care?",
    answer:
      "Self-care is the practice of intentionally taking time and actions to prioritize your physical, mental, and emotional well-being. It involves activities and behaviors that nourish and rejuvenate you, ultimately promoting a healthier and more balanced life.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: " bg-[#FDE4CF] ",
  },
  {
    question: "Why is self-care important?",
    answer:
      "Self-care is crucial because it helps reduce stress, prevent burnout, and improve overall quality of life. It enables you to maintain good physical and mental health, enhance resilience, and better cope with life's challenges.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#D0FDD5]",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I know what self-care activities are right for me?",
    answer:
      "Finding the right self-care activities requires self-awareness. Reflect on what activities make you feel relaxed, happy, and reenergized. It might be reading, exercising, meditating, spending time with loved ones, or engaging in a hobby. Experiment with different activities to see what works best for you.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#FDE4CF]",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I make self-care a regular part of my routine?",
    answer:
      "To make self-care a habit, schedule it into your daily or weekly routine. Prioritize it like any other important task. Set boundaries to protect your self-care time and communicate its significance to those around you",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#D0FDD5]",
  },
  {
    question: "Are there different types of self-care?",
    answer: `Yes, self-care can be categorized into several types:
      - Physical self-care: Activities that promote physical health, such as exercise, healthy eating, and adequate sleep.
      - Mental self-care: Practices that support mental well-being, such as mindfulness, journaling, and learning new skills.
      - Emotional self-care: Techniques to manage emotions and reduce stress, such as talking to a therapist, practicing self-compassion, and seeking support from friends.
      - Social self-care: Spending quality time with loved ones and nurturing relationships.
      - Spiritual self-care: Engaging in activities that connect you with your beliefs and values, like meditation, prayer, or spending time in nature.`,
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#FDE4CF]",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should I do when I feel guilty about taking time for self-care?",
    answer:
      "It's common to feel guilty initially, but remember that self-care is essential for your well-being. Try reframing your perspective by recognizing that taking care of yourself enables you to be better for others. Over time, as you experience the benefits, the guilt may subside.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#D0FDD5]",
  },
  {
    question: "Can self-care be adapted to different life circumstances?",
    answer:
      "Yes, self-care is adaptable. You can tailor your self-care routine to your current life circumstances. In times of high stress or busyness, it might involve shorter, more frequent self-care activities. Flexibility is key to maintaining self-care.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#FDE4CF]",
  },
  {
    question: "What are some simple self-care practices I can start with?",
    answer: `Simple self-care practices include:
      - Taking short breaks during the day to stretch and breathe.
      - Practicing deep breathing exercises.
      - Listening to calming music.
      - Enjoying a warm bath or shower.
      - Spending a few minutes in nature.
      - Disconnecting from electronic devices for a set period.`,
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#D0FDD5]",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I involve others in my self-care routine?",
    answer:
      "You can involve loved ones in your self-care routine by sharing your goals and preferences with them. Ask for their support and invite them to participate in activities that promote mutual well-being, such as going for a walk together or trying a new hobby as a group.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#FDE4CF]",
  },
  {
    question: "What should I do if I'm struggling to prioritize self-care?",
    answer:
      "If you find it challenging to prioritize self-care, consider seeking guidance from a therapist or counselor. They can help you explore underlying issues and develop strategies to make self-care a sustainable and fulfilling part of your life.",
    user_image: "path/to/image",
    bg: "bg-[#D0FDD5]",
  },
];

export const avatars = [
  avatarImage1,
  avatarImage2,
  avatarImage3,
  avatarImage4,
  avatarImage5,
  avatarImage6,
];
